Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel Stock
Time. In this video, we
will talk about some companies
that are trading on Fox yesterday because we are
seeing good news about them today.
Which are those companies and
what news is there in them? Before starting the discussion on this,
I would like to say that if
you have not subscribed to our channel,
please subscribe and click the bell icon.
First of all, we will talk about
Aavlon Technology. Today, this company has been
listed in the stock market and with a discount of 1%, that is, it has been listed at
1% less than its base price. The
listing of this company has been done
at 431 shares, whereas its
price band
is 436, that is, it has been listed at a decrease of more than 1%. In
a way, investors have been
disappointed. The
news in this is that Gold Ma Sax has
bought shares in this company.
He has bought shares in this company for Rs 32 crore 63 lakh issued in the open market. He has
bought 1
lakh 45 thousand shares and
these are at
408 13 paise.  They have made
this purchase based on shares, so because of this, this share can go
into the red tomorrow. You can keep an eye on it.
However, Gold Band Sex Fund,
Gold Ma Sex India Equity
Portfolio has also acquired
3.5 lakh shares in this company and
they have acquired 412 shares based on shares, so
you can keep an eye on it because it has been
listed today and this share
can go into the red tomorrow as well. Apart from this, if we
talk about ICC Security now, then today a
rise of 1% was seen in its shares, there was greenery of about 2%
in it. Tomorrow this company will
release its quarterly results, so you
can keep an eye on it as well.
Apart from this, Master Tata Communication
Industries,
Gujarat Hotels will
also release its quarterly earnings tomorrow, so
due to this, it can go into the red.
You can keep an eye on it.
You can keep an eye on it because the news is
that the company has released its quarterly
results and it has shown a huge rise of 40%
in its profit. The company
says that its total profit for the quarter is
437 crores. Apart from this, if we
talk about net premium earning, then the
company has shown a growth of more than 12% in that too.
According to Rauniyar, it says that the
total net premium earning has been ₹726 crores.
Apart from this, there has been an increase of
13.3% in total income. It says
that the
total income of the company is ₹5256 crores.
Talking about its combined ratio,
its combined ratio has been
104.2% in this quarter,
whereas in the last year's quarter it was
103.5
%. Currently, the company has
also announced the final dividend. For this, it has
said that
look at the final dividend, due to this, this share can
remain in the market, you can keep an eye on it.
Apart from this, if we talk about the
size of Tata Coffee, then you can keep an eye on it as well.
Although there was no significant increase in its shares today,
but the news in this is that  The
company has released its quarterly
results, showing a 20%
growth in its consolidated profit. The
company says that its consolidated profit is Rs 48 crore per
quarter. The
reason given for this is that
other income has been good
and there was less expenditure on taxes, due to which the
company's profit has seen a 20% increase.
It said that
there has been a
growth of 10.5% in consolidated revenue. Its consolidated
revenue was Rs
723 crore. There has been a
decline of 4.8% compared to last year. According to the report,
its profit has been Rs 105 crore 72 lakh.
And the margin has also seen a decline of
230 basis points.
Due to all this,
its impact can be seen in the company's shares.
You can keep an eye on it.
Today, some big news has also been seen in Bank of India,
although today its
shares did not see much increase.
But fluctuations were seen throughout the day. The
news in this is that the company had a
meeting of people for fundraising, in which the
board of directors has given approval
for fundraising of Rs. 6500 crore. This fundraising will be
of Rs. 4500 crore, while Rs.
2000 crore will be
Basel III complete,
so due to this this stock can also remain in the fox,
you can keep an eye on it.
If we talk about its performance of the last 5 days, then a fall of
5.5 percent is being seen in it.
Talking about the stock of State Bank of India,
fluctuations were seen throughout the day, although this
company had
made a high of 548 paise and
made 540, while its opening was around 545 paise.
Today the news is being seen in this
that its
Committee of Central Board has given approval, the company is going to raise
two billion dollars for fundraising,
this will be done gradually, a
fall of more than 3% is being seen in this. The
news in this is  It is known that the
United States Food and Drug
Administration,
also known as USFDA, has approved the
Estrole
System. The
company will manufacture and market this system. Therefore, due to
this, the stock
could remain in the red tomorrow. You can keep an eye on it.
Apart from this,
you can also keep an eye on Peedhi Light Industries tomorrow.
Today, its shares saw a fall of more than 2.5%. There are
also reports about this. The
company has signed
an agreement with a paste company called Adhesive ICC.
What will this company do? You
can also keep an eye on State Projects Limited. A
decline of around 5% was seen.
If we talk about the performance of both, then there is a
decline of around 2.5%. But
in one month it has increased by more than 7%,
whereas in 6 months it will see a slight decline. The
news in this is that its
subsidiary company, Prestige
Agora Business Park, has
acquired 51% shares of Darshan Tech Park. In return, this
company will pay Rs 66 crore. Therefore, due to this, the stock
could remain in the red tomorrow. You should keep an eye on this.  If you can keep it,
friends, I hope you
liked our video. Do
not forget to tell us in our comment box how you liked it. Also,
subscribe to our channel and
press the bell icon.
Thank you very much for watching the video.